Preliminary Inventory to the Carla A. Hills Papers, 1964-1993
Hoover Institution Archives
- HPMC Organization
- Housing Starts
- HUD Child Care Center
- HUD/Commerce /Labor - Interagency Demonstration Program
- HUD-Department of Agriculture Report FY 74
- HUD Description
- HUD Map
- HUD Studies
- HUD-VA Joint Certification Green Card
- Hunter, J. Robert
- Income Assistance Simplification Act
- Impoundment Issues
- Independence Plaza North
- Indian Matters
- Inequities Funds
- Inflation Impact Statements
- Information Task Force
- Innovative Projects Program
- Inspector General Monthly Report
- Inspector General -- Annual Report
- Inspector General (Thomas)
- Insurance Claims Correspondence
- Interagency Committees
- Interagency Fair Housing Agreement between HUD/FPC
- Interagency Fair Housing Agreement between Department of Justice/HUD
- Interagency Agreement Between HUD/DOL re Federal Agency
  - Advanced Fair Housing/Location of Government Sponsored Facilities
- Interagency Fair Housing Agreement between HUD/Consumer Product Safety Commission
- Interagency Fair Housing Agreement between HUD/USDA
- Interagency Drought Committee
- Intergovernmental Personnel Assignment (IPA)
- International Affairs
- International Calendar
- International Women's Year (Box 19)
- Interdepartmental Task Force for International Women's Year
- Interstate Land Sales Registration (OILSR) (McDowell)
  - Interstate Land Sales Full Disclosure Act Correspondence
- INVITATIONS, (Brown Folder)
  - Invitations Accepted - Vol. #6 -, May 1976 - December 1976
  - Invitations Accepted - Vol. #6 -, January 1977
  - Invitations Declined - Vol. #5 -, May 1976 - January 1977
    - a. Background on Declinations
    - b. Items with Questions
- Job Opportunities Program
- Joint Committee on Tall Buildings
- Joint Economic Committee Hearings -, July 18, 1975
- Joint Economic Committee Hearings -, September 23, 1976
- Joint HUD - USDA Rural Demonstration Delivery System for Community Development/Housing Assistance
- Joint Treasury/Federal Financing Bank, HUD and OMB Working Group
- Kaufman, Broad
- Kelly, Bill
- Kennedy Center Schedule
- Kettering Foundation
- Kramer, Ferd
- Kraus, Charles - (Washington Post Interview), 12/15/76
- Labor
  - Labor Management
  - President's Labor Management Committee
  - Labor Standards
  - Labor Leadership Meeting
- Labor Relations (HUD)
- Land Use Planning (Box 20)
- Lander, Clifton P. Jr.
- Lead Base Paint Hearings Extension/Modification of Lead Base Paint Act, S.1664
- Lefcoe Study (Professor George) "Causes of Defaults) Foreclosures in FHA Single Family Mortgage Insurance Programs"
- Legal Honors Interns -- Meeting with CAH, 11/13/75
- Legal Opinions
- Legislative Affairs Abstracts
- Legislative Affairs Memoranda
- Legislative Program for FY-76
- Legislative Hearing Schedule
- Leonard, Frank M.
- Levine, Gerald G., Special Assistant to CAH
- Life Insurance Luncheon with Chief Executive Officers
- Limited Rehabs
- Liquidating Funds (Revolving Fund)
- Litigation Reports
- Local Housing Authorities
- Local Public Works Capital Development/Investment Act of, 1975
  - (Anti-Cyclical Bill)
  - H. R. 11860 Brown's Alternative
  - Press
  - Correspondence
  - Veto
  - HUD Alternative Proposal
  - Background with Notes
  - Public Works Employment Act of - S.3201 Veto, 1976
- Losses from Sale of HUD-Owned Home Properties (Ad Hoc Working Group)
- Low Rent Public Housing (LRPH) Operating Data
- Luncheon Bills
- NAHA Meeting in Chicago with Gail Cincotta, 10/20/75
- Management
- Management and Control of Growth PD&R Research Product
- MBO (Management by Objectives)
- Mansion House Litigation
- Marina Cypress Apartments
- Maritime Affairs/Activities
- Marquette Park - AKA Chicago Lawn (Box 21)
- Medearis, Robert W.
- Medical Malpractice
- Merit System
- Methunion Manor Section 221 (d) (3)
- Metropolis Speaks and Listening to the Metropolis - HUD Research Project, Executive Summary
- Meyers, Charles J.
- Miami Proposal
- Michigan State Housing Development Authority (MSHDA)
- Minimum Property Standards
- Minority Banks Program
- Minority Business Development Public and Private Section Performance FY 75
- Minority Public Administrators
- Miscellaneous - HUD
- Miscellaneous News Articles
- Mission Park
- Mississippi - Project #065-44803/#065-44801 - Santa Maria Delmar; Villa Maria Apartments
- Mobile Homes (Brown Folder)
  - Mobile Homes Miscellaneous
  - Volume 1 - National Mobile HOmes Construction and Safety Act Standards Act Correspondence
  - Volume 2 - Federal Mobile Home Construction and Safety Standards Act Correspondence
  - National Council of States on Building Codes and Standards
  - National Mobile Home Advisory Council
  - Improvements needed in Mobil Homes Park Mortgage Insurance Program (GAO Report to Congress)
  - Mobile Home Omnibus (H. R. 9852)
- Model Cities Planning Council GAO Report
- Moderates
- Modernization Program
- Modified Cost Approach
- Mortgage Backed Securities
- Mortgage Bankers Association of America (MBA)
- Mortgage Credit Hearings Before State Subcommittee on Housing and Urban Affairs
- Mortgage Insurance Companies of America (MICA)
- Mortgage LImits
- Mortgage Servicing/HUD Property Management, Hearing before Committee on Government Operations, Subcommittee on Manpower/Housing
- Mortgage Market Study
- Mortgage Letters (re Assignment of Home Mortgages), 76-9/75-10 (Box 22)
- Mortgagee Monitoring/Surveillance
  - Mortgagee Monitoring/Surveillance Vol. 2, January
  - Mortgagee Servicing Regulations
  - Mortgagee Surveillance
- Morton, Rogers C. B.
- Multifamily Construction Tax Treatment
- Multifamily Default Hearing
- Multifamily Housing
- Multifamily Property Disposition
- Multifamily Starts
- Ballooning
- McGraw, Richard L.
- NAACP - National Housing Corporation Annual Report, 1975
- National Advisory Committee on Juvenile Justice and Delinquency Prevention
- National Advisory Council for Career Education
- National Advisory Council on Extension/Continuing Education
- National Apartment Association
- National Association of Homebuilders General
- NAHB - Home Owners Warranty (HOW)
- National Association of Homebuilders HOusing Summit
- National Association of Housing and Redevelopment Officials
  - (NAHEO), (Brown Folder)
  - General
  - Meeting of July 17, 1975
- National Association of Mutual Savings Banks
- National Association of Real Estate Brokers (NAREB) Meeting of 7/18/75
- National Association of Realtors Correspondence/Miscellaneous
- National Association of REaltors Home Protection Program
- National Association of Regional Councils Boston, Mass., 5/28/75 (Box 23)
- National Black Republican Council Meeting of, December 12, 1975
- National Center for Housing Management
- National Conference on the Urban Environment
- National Corporation of Housing Partnerships
- National Council on the Aging
- National Energy Information Center
- National Environmental Policy Act
- National Equal Employment Opportunity Affirmative Action Plan - FY 76
- National Federation of Settlement and Neighborhood Centers
- National Forrest Products Association
- National Flood Insurance Program Regulations
- National Gas Survey Advisory Committees and Task Froces
- National Governors Conference New Orleans, Louisiana, 6/8-10/75
  - Briefing Book from Public Affairs
  - Folder #1 Speech - Drafts/Final
  - Folder Correspondence/Background
- National Growth and Development Housing Banking Currency/ Housing Subcommittee Hearings -, 9/75
- National Hispanic Coalition for Better Housing
- National Housing Conference (Folder)
- National Housing Rehabilitation Association (Folder)
- National Institute of Building Sciences (NIBS)
- National Insurance Development Funds Advisory Board
- National Jewish Hospital and Research Center
- National League of Cities
- National Newspaper Association Government Affairs Conference, 3/14/75
- National Science Foundation
- National Secretaries Week
- National Security Council Undersecretary's Committee Development of State
- National Trails System Act Public Law 90-543
- National Urban Coalition
- National Urban League Meeting of, September 17, 1976
- National Urban Strategy
- National Women's Political Caucus
- Neighborhood Facility
- NEIGHBORHOOD REVITALIZATION)President's Committee) (Box 23-A)
  - White House Announcement
  - House Banking, Currency, Housing Committee, Housing/Community Development Subcommittee
  - Housing National Neighborhood Policy Act, 9/9/76
  - Testimony and Press
  - News Clips
  - Work Papers
  - Neighborhood Revitalization
  - President's Committee - Report
  - General Correspondence
  - Revitalization-Pittsburgh -, 8/25/76
  - Revitalization-Baltimore -, 8/6/76
  - Revitalization-Newark -, 8/12/76
- URBAN DEVELOPMENT AND NEIGHBORHOOD REVITALIZATION
  (President's Committee)
- PRESIDENT'S COMMITTEE - Draft Report
- PRESIDENT'S COMMITTEE ON URBAN DEVELOPMENT AND NEIGHBORHOOD REVITALIZATION -- Meeting with Father Geno Baroni -, 7/28/76
- SCHEDULE FOR BALITMORE, MARYLAND
- New Community Board of Directors Conference Call -, 12/2/75 (Box 24)
- New Community Board of Directors
- New Community Regulations
- New Community Title X
- New Community Task Forces on Intergovernmental Cooperation
- New Communities -- Business Plan
- New Communities (Folder)
  - New Communities Administration (Stolz)
  - New Community Oversight Hearing
  - New Community Projects (General)
  - Flower Mound New Town Limited
  - Granada
  - Maumelle
  - New Fields
  - Soul City
  - Columbia
  - San Antonio Ranch
- New Communities (Draft Report) Booz, Allen White Paper
- Newman, Constance (Box 25)
- New Policy Executives Briefing Program
- New Towns
- Noise Correspondence
- Occupational Safety and Health Administration
- Official Portrait (CAH)
- OMB Chron File as of, 12/1/75
- OMB - Management Initiatives
- OMB
- Opportunities Industrialization Centers
- Order of Succession
- Organization of HUD Re: Proper Role of Regional and Area Offices
- Organizational Handbook
- Organization Conference
- Organization Task Forces
  - Organization Conference, 2/25/76
  - Staffing Allocations/Flexibility TAsk Force
  - Administrative Support Task Force
  - Duplicate Processing Task Force
  - FIA Staff Task Force Reporting Relationship in Field
  - Coopers and Lybrand Report
- Overlap Function HM and FD (Box 26)
- Oversight Hearings (House) on Administration of the National Environmental Policy Act (NEPA), 8/17/75
- Oversight Hearings (House) on Section 8 Program and Implementation of 1975 Emergency Housing Act - 730
- Oversight Hearings (Senate) Section 8 and Community Development Block Grant Program, June 12, 1975
- Oversight Hearings (House) Section 8 and Community Development
- Oversight Hearings (Senate) Committee on Banking, Housing and Urban Affairs Re: Section 8 Revised 235 Foreclosures and Insurance Funds, November 5, 1975
- Oversight Hearings (Senate) Housing Goals -, February 20, 1976
- Oversight Hearings (Senate) Fair Housing Lending Practices, 3/12/76
- Oversight Hearings (Senate) Field Of Housing/Community Development, 6/23/76
- Pacific - Northwest Regional Commission
- Pacific Trust Territories
- Paprin, Morris S. - meeting with CAH and Other New York Area Builders and Developers, 1/29/76
- Parking
- Parks Proposal
- Parma Matter - CDBG Application
- Pending Bills
- Performance Evaluation
- Performance Funding System
- Personnel (CURVEY) Vol. #2, January 1975-December 1976
- Personnel (CAH Immediate Staff)
- Personnel Activities and Accomplishments for FY 75 Report
- Personnel Management Evaluation
- Pilgrim Society Museum
- Planned Unit Developments
- Policy Development and Research (PD&R) (Orlebeke)
- Policy Meetings
- Political Issues
- Pontiac, Michigan, 4/9/76
- Preservation Service of the National Trust Advisory Committee
  - Compliance Issue
- Presidential Classroom for Young Americans
- Presidential Clemancy Board
- Presidential Cost Reduction Campaign
- Presidential Two-Year Report
- President's Committee on Employment of the Handicapped
- Privacy Act of, 1974
- Procurements Statistical REport
- Program Activity Reports
- Program Evaluation - FY 76
- Project Management System
- Property Disposition
- Property Disposition Investigation by House Government Operations Manpower and Housing Subcommittee (Box 27)
- PROP (Property Release Option Program)
- Proposal to Stimulate Housing Industry
- Proposal for Financing National Income Housing
- PRUITT-IGOE
- Public Affairs - Vol. #5, April - January 77
- Public Facilities Loan Program
- Public Housing Agencies (Tenant Management Demonstrations)
  - Public Housing Projects
- Public Interest Groups
- Public Service Briefing Program for Policy Executives
- Purchase Money Mortgages
- People United to Save Humanity (PUSH)
  - Meeting of November 19, 1975
  - First Meeting
- Reagan
- Real Estate Investment Trusts Reits
- Real Estate Settlements Procedure Act - Amendments of 1975
- Real Estate Settlement Procedure Act of, 1974
- Real Estate Settlements procedure Act of (RESPA Joint Economic Committee Hearings -- ), 1974 9/75
- Recertification of Income
- Real Estate Tax Credit
- Recruiting
  - Recruiting (General) Vol. II, October 1975 - Sept. 76
  - Federal Insurance Administration (Recruiting)
  - HM Recruiting
  - HPMC (Recruiting General)
  - Interns (Recruiting)
  - Recruiting OILSR
  - New Communities Recruiting
  - Recruiting (Public Affairs)
  - Special Assistants Recruiting
  - GNMA
- International Affairs Recruiting (Box 28)
- Recruiting Closed
  - Recruiting General -, March - September 1975
  - Consumer Affairs Recruiting
  - Deputy Assistant Secretary - EO
  - Assistant Secretary HPMC - FHA Commissioner
  - Inspector General (Recruiting)
  - Assistant Secretary PD&R
  - Speechwriter (Recruiting)
  - Under Secretary (Recruiting)
- Redlining
- Reduction in Force (RIF)
- Regulations and Issuance Process
- Regs Unit
- Priority List of Issuances
- Priority List of Regulations
- Earthquake Regulations
- Public Housing Regulations
- REGS
  - CPD Regs
  - EO Regulations
  - HM Regs
  - Regulations re FHA Insurance of Advances on Off Sight Building Components
  - Letters of Credit
  - Regs - Mobile Home Construction and Safety Standards
  - Relocation Regulations
  - Coinsurance Regs - State Housing Agencies
  - Mortgage Servicing Regulations
  - New York City Multifamily Projects
  - Rent Regulations
  - Section 212 Regulations
  - Section 213 Regulations
  - Section 301 Regulations
  - Standard of Conduct Regulation
  - Title I, Emergency Homeowners' Relief Program Regulations
  - Utilities - Separate Meter Regs.
- Regs Section 3
- Regulations - Status of Section 8 and Section 202 (Box 29)
- Regulations - re - Deeds in Lieu of Foreclosure
- Regulations - Section 203 - FHA Mortgage Insurance
- Section 8 Advertising Regulations
- Regulations - Agency/Congressional/Judicial Review of Procedures and Public Comments
- Regulations - Tenant Eviction
- Section 235 - Reactivation of Suspended Homeownership - Subsidy Program Regulations
  - Regulations - Section 235 Overpayments Collection
- Regulations - Financing Fire Safety Equipment for Health Care Facilities
- Regulations - Supplemental Allocation Based on Areawide Housing Opportunity Plans
- Regulations - Sewer Treatment
- Regulatory Perform Program
- Rehabilitation Demonstration
- Rehabilitation Correspondence
- Rehabilitation Task Force
- Relocation
- Rents
- Rent Supplement Program
- Rent Supplement - Payment Monitoring Reports
- Report of U. S. Commission on Civil Rights
- Republican Convention
  - Acceptance Speech
  - National Federation of Republican Women
- Republican Leadership Meeting
- Requests for Proposals
- Requests for Proposals - Fair Housing Evaluation Title VIII Enforcement
- HUD Research Efforts
  - Master Plan of Research
  - Secretarial Research
- Residential Construction Industry
- Crawford, H. R.
- Resignation Letters HUD (Box 30)
- Revenue Sharing
- Rosen, Kenneth - Joint Center for Urban Studies MIR-Harvard University
- Rosenbaum, Richard M.
- Ross, Barbara, et al. v. Hills, Carla A. et al., USDC D. of Maryland CA #H-75-506
- Rural Affairs
- Safe Drinking Water Act
- Safety Devices
- Safety '76 Campaign
- San Francisco Housing Authority
- Savings Bond Campaign, (1976)
- Scenic Rivers Assn. et. al. v. LYNN, et. al. 10CA #74-131-C
- School Litigation (HEW/HUD)
- Schwartz, Jonathan B.
- Secchia, Peter
- Secondary Wage Rate Agreement
- Secretary's Discretionary Grant Fund
- Secretary Held Mortgages
- Section 8 Annual Contributions Contract
- Section 8 and Conventional Public Housing
  - Subsidy Assistance for Loan Management and Property Disposition
  - Task Force
- Section 8 - LM (Site/Neighborhood Standards)
- Section 8 Fair Share Plans Allocation
- Section 8 Existing Reconnaissance Study
- Section 8 New Construction Program
- Section 8 Fair Market Rents
- Section 8 Field Trade of Units
- Section 8 Monitoring System
- Section 8 Regional Administrators Meeting, 5/18/76
- Section 8 Site Selection Criteria
- Section 8 Housing Assistance Payments Program (Box 31)
- Section and Conventional Public Housing Task Force
- Section 8 Rehabilitation Program
- Section 8 Proposed Amendments -- Hearings before Subcommittee on Housing/Community Development, 10/22/75
- Section 8 Reporting System
- Section 8 Training
- Section 23 Project - Leased Housing Program for Low-income Families
- Section 106 (Elderly)
- Section 202 Selection Committee Task Force Application Vol. #3, March
- Section 202 Selection Committee Task Force - Vol. #2, Feb. 1976
- Section 202 Selection Committee Task Force - Vol. #1, September - January 1976
- Section 202
  - Section 202 Supplemental Appropriation
  - Section 202 Regulation
  - Section 202 Program Issues
  - Section 202 Direct Loan Programs
  - Section 202 Housing Hearings on Elderly
  - Section 202 Senate Hearings on Elderly Housing Program
  - Ad Hoc Housing Coalition re Section 202
  - Section 202 House Select Committee on Aging Hearings on Elderly Housing, 9/10/76
- Section 203 Foreclosures
- Section 223F
  - Section 223f
  - Coinsurance and 223f
- Section 235 Correspondence - Vol. #2 -, July 76 thru December 76 (Box 32)
- Section 235 Correspondence - Vol. #1 -, June 75 thru August 76
- Section 235 -- Income Limits
- Section 235 -- Reactivation of Suspended Homeownership Subsidy Program
- Section 235 -- Reactivation of Suspended Homeownership Subsidy Program
  - Reactivation of Suspended Homeownership Subsidy Program Legislation
  - Reactivation of Suspended Homeownership Subsidy Program Charts
  - Reactivation of Suspended Homeownership Subsidy Program Press
  - Reactivation of Suspended Homeownership Subsidy Program Fact Sheet Package
  - Reactivation of Suspended Homeownership Subsidy Program Handwritten Notes
  - Reactivation of Suspended Homeownership Subsidy Program Q's and A's
  - Reactivation of Suspended Homeownership Subsidy Program Drafts
- Section 236 -- Income LImits Administrative Judgement
- Section 236 -- Roll-Over Authority
- Section 236 -- Recession of Admission Income Limits
- Section 236 -- Return of Excess Income to Mortgages
- Section 236 -- Operating Subsidy Litigation
- Section 236 -- Task Force
- Section 236
  - Section 236 Projects
  - Javitz Bill to Amend Section 236
  - Section 236 Report (B-114863) of the Comptroller General of the U. S. re Housing for the Elderly
  - Uplands Apartments Project Section 236 Baltimore, Maryland - REnt Strike
  - Section 236 Woodlands (New Community)
- LA Proposal on HUD Property Disposition
- Section 312 -- Rehabilitation Loan Program
- Rural Areas Mortgage Credit Section 511
- Section 515 -- Rural Demonstration
- Construction Repair Inspections Section 518 (b)
- Section 518 (b)
- Section 802 (Box 33)
  - Section 802
  - Urban Reinvestment - Co-insurance Act
  - Co-insurance Program
  - Co-insurance Program (HUD) Second Annual Report on Congress, 3/1/76
  - Multifamily -- Co-insurance State Agency
  - Section 802 -- Interest Subsidies for State Bonds
  - State Housing Finance Agencies
  - Section 822 -- Treasury/HUD Report to Congress
    re: Effects of Alternative Methods of Financing Section 236/802
- Section 805 -- Enforcement of Title VIII of the Civil Rights Act of, 1968
- Section 815 -- Special Needs Demonstration
- Selection of Sites for Federal Facilities
- Sequoia
- Service Charges (Restructuring)
- Seventh Biennial HUD Awards for Design Excellence
- Sex Discrimination (Task Force) D/J, Civil Rights Division
- Sign Control
- Single Family Housing
- Single Family -- Defaults (Mortgagee Servicing REquirements)
- Sixth Annual Report on Government Services to Rural America
- Sky Tower Litigation: Cole et al. v. Lynn et al. USDC D.D.C. No. 74-1872
- Small Business Administration
- Solar Energy
  - Solar Energy and Cooling Demonstration Act (Correspondence)
  - Solar Energy
  - Solar Energy Hearings
- Southern Regional Council Report
- Space
- Space Shuttle Meeting, 7/21/75
- Spanish Speaking Americans
- Special Inter-agency Task Force re: Evacuation of Vietnam
- Split Interest Rate
- Staff Luncheon Notes
- Staff Meetings
- Standard Metropolitan Statistical Area (SMSA) Discretionary Funding
- Status of Major HUD Programs
- Stegall, Ronald C. (Box 34)
- Stimulating Building
- Stoppello, Diana
- Subsidy Cost Comparions of Section 235/Section 8 (FHA-insured) Assisted Housing Programs Serving Family of Four, (2 Minors)
- Subsidy Cost Comparisons for Section 8 v. Section 236 and Conventional Public Housing
- Federal Summer Employment Program for Youth
- Sun-Times Allegation (Chicago Housing Authority)
- Supergrade Allocations
- Supply of Mortgage Credit --, 1970 -74
- Swearing-in Ceremonies (General)
- Swearing in Ceremony Newman/Dausch
- Systems and Methods usedfor Processing and Servicing Mortgage Insurance Accounting Activities
- Taino Towers
- Taino Towers Briefing
- Tandem
  - Tandem Mortgage Purchase Funds for Multifamily Housing - Vol. #2
  - Tandem Mortgage Purchase Funds for Multifamily Housing - Vol. #1
  - Tandem (Use of Funds)
  - Tandem Multifamily Conventional Program
  - Section 8 Proposal
  - Senate Oversight Hearings
- Target Projects Program (TPP)
- Task Forces
- Tax (Mortgage Interest Tax Deduction)
- Tax Shelters Task Force
- Taxes on Acquired Properties
- Thaxton, Warren
- Theft -- $1.2 Million
- Timber Products
- Title I Delegation of Authority with Respect to Discretionary Grants in Behalf of New Communities
- Title I Housing Act of Amended Report of Urban Renewal Operations, 1949
- Title I, Emergency Housing Act of - Foreclosures Task Force, 1975
- Title I - Emergency Homeowners' Relief Act - First Report to Congress, 8/29/75 (Box 35)
- Title I - Emergency Homeowners' Relief Act - Second Report to Congress, 10/30/75
- Emergency Homeowners' Relief Act - Third Report to Congress, 12/30/75
- Title I - Emergency Homeowners' Relief Act - Fourth Report to Congress, 2/27/76
- Title I - Emergency Homeowners' Relief Act - Fifth Report to Congress, 4/27/76
- Title I - Emergency Homeowners' Relief Act - Sixth Report to Congress, 6/25/76
- Title I - Emergency Homeowners' Relief Act - Seventh Report to Congress, 8/24/76
- Title I - Emergency Homeowners' Relief Act - Eighth Report to Congress, 10/22/76
- Title I - Emergency Homeowners' Relief Act - Ninth Report to Congress, 12/23/76
- Title II - Emergency Housing Act of - Tandem Authority, 1975
- Training
- Transition
- Transition to New Fiscal Year - OMB Bulletin No. 75-9 Legislative Changes
- Travel Legislation
- Travel - CAH - HUD
- HUD - U/S CHRON FILE -, March 1975
- Under Secretary Memoranda
- Underwriting Procedures
- Unemployment
- Unified Issuance System
- U. S. Conference of Mayors - Milwaukee, Wisconsin, 6/30/75
- U. S. Conference of Mayors (General)
- U. S. - Iran Working Group on Housing
- U. S. League of Savings Association
- United States Railway Association
- U. S. - U.S.S.R. Agreement on Cooperation in Housing and Other Construction
- University Gardens Project
- Urban Counties
- Urban Development Corporation
- Urban Intern Program